seoceros.com 2017-03-14

# Privacy Policy

As you use our services, we want you to be clear how we’re using information and the ways in which you can protect your privacy.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  1. What information we collect and why we collect it.
  2. How we use that information.

We’ve tried to keep it as simple as possible, but if you’re not familiar with terms like cookies, IP addresses, pixel tags and browsers, then read about these key terms first. Your privacy matters to SEOCEROS so whether you are new to SEOCEROS or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices. Most of your questions are answered on this page.

**_Information that SEOCEROS collects_**

We collect information to provide better services to all of our users.

**_We collect information in two ways:_**

  1. **Information you give us.**  When you register or contact us, we might ask for personal information, like your name, address, email address or telephone number.
  2. **Information we get from your use of our services.**   This information includes:

_Device information:_

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network information including phone number). 

_Log information_

When you use our services or view content provided by SEOCEROS, we might automatically collect and store certain information in server logs. This may include:

  * Details of how you used our service, such as your search queries.
  * IP address.
  * Cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

_Cookies and anonymous identifiers_

Our partners and we use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a SEOCEROS service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners.

**_How we use information we collect_**

We use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect SEOCEROS and our users.

We will ask for your consent before using information for a purpose other than those that are set out in this Privacy Policy.

SEOCEROS processes personal information on our servers in many countries around the world. We may process your personal information on a server located outside the country where you live.

If you are in the progress of developing your website and you do not want to make your website to appear on seoceros.com amongst the published analyses, please insert the following code : < meta name = " seoceros " content = " noindex "> into your main page under the <head > section. When you are done, please run an analysis again on seoceros.com. After we detect this code, your website will be deleted from our published analyses automatically within 24 hours.

**_Information we share_**

We do not share personal information with companies, organisations and individuals outside of SEOCEROS unless one of the following circumstances applies:

With your consent

We will share personal information with companies, organisations or individuals outside of SEOCEROS when we have your consent to do so. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

_For external processing_

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

_For legal reasons_

We will share personal information with companies, organisations or individuals outside of SEOCEROS if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, and preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

  * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of SEOCEROS, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**We may share aggregated** , non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services.

**_Information security_**

  * We work hard to protect SEOCEROS and our users from unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular:
  * We encrypt many of our services using SSL.
  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorised access to systems.

We restrict access to personal information to SEOCEROS employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

**_When this Privacy Policy applies_**

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by SEOCEROS.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you in our analysis results, sites that may include SEOCEROS services, or other sites linked from our services.

Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organisations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads.

**_Changes_**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page so please check back regularly.
